(Raj(internally, while Penny continues to talk):)Oh, my. She does smell good.
What is that? Vanilla?
You know?
(Penny:)Where I come from, someone comes
into your house at night, you shoot.
(Penny:)Okay? And you don't shoot to wound.
I mean, all right, my sister shot her husband,
but it was an accident, they were drunk.
(Penny:)What was I saying?
(Raj(internally):)She's so chatty.
Maybe my parents were right.
Maybe I'd be better off with an Indian girl.
(Raj(internally):)We'd have
the same cultural background...
...and my wife could sing to my children
the lullabies my mother sang to me.
It's obvious they meant well.
(Penny:)I'm having a really rough time.
Like I said...
(Penny:)...I broke up with my boyfriend
and it's freaking me out.
[RAJESH SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE
IN VOICE-OVER]
(Penny:)I mean, just because most of the men
I've known happened to be jerks...
(Penny:)...doesn't mean I should just assume
Leonard and Sheldon are.
(Sheldon:)Right?
(Raj(internally):)She asked me a question.
I should probably nod.
(Penny:)That's exactly what I thought.
(Penny:)Thank you for listening. You're a doll.